TIRTA SAMARA

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Bandung, Indonesia +6281284964533 Tirta4132@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a creative and experienced web front end developer with expertise in designing engaging and responsive user interfaces. With a background in modern web development, I possess in-depth knowledge of the latest technologies and design trends, enabling me to create optimal user experiences.

LANGUAGE SKILL

Html, Css, JS, PHP UI Design: Figma Bahasa Indonesia **English**

framework: Laravel, React

JS, Next JS

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering, Universitas Komputer Indonesia

Studying at Universitas Komputer Indonesia majoring in Informatics Engineering

Vocational School 2017 - 2020

Studied Bogor 3 State Vocational High School

WORK EXPERIENCE

Network technical

Indonesia, Diskominfo

January 2019 - June 2019

• During my internship at Kominfo as a network technician, I gained valuable hands-on experience in designing, installing, and maintaining computer networks. I learned how to troubleshoot various network issues and worked with a team to ensure that all systems were up and running smoothly.

Freelance 2021 - Now

 As a freelance front-end web developer, I specialize in crafting stunning and responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and frameworks like React And Next JS.

PORTFOLIO

https://portfoliotirta.vercel.app/

2021 - Now